<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ryan Safner</title>
    <link>https://upbeat-mcclintock-05ba11.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ryan Safner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://upbeat-mcclintock-05ba11.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>https://upbeat-mcclintock-05ba11.netlify.app/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://upbeat-mcclintock-05ba11.netlify.app/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>https://upbeat-mcclintock-05ba11.netlify.app/posts/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://upbeat-mcclintock-05ba11.netlify.app/posts/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DERA</title>
      <link>https://upbeat-mcclintock-05ba11.netlify.app/portfolio/dera/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://upbeat-mcclintock-05ba11.netlify.app/portfolio/dera/</guid>
      <description>This is a Java reference implementation of dynamic event-driven actors runtime aiming at providing adequate abstraction levels and mechanisms for modelling and developing (distributed) event-based systems. DERA leverages the intrinsic loose coupling of event-driven communication styles to support various kinds of run-time evolution and adaptation (i.e., enabling run-time flexibility) while minimizing the non-deterministic nature of traditional event-based applications (i.e., supporting formal analysis).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hyde-hyde</title>
      <link>https://upbeat-mcclintock-05ba11.netlify.app/portfolio/hyde-hyde/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://upbeat-mcclintock-05ba11.netlify.app/portfolio/hyde-hyde/</guid>
      <description>Hyde-hyde is a responsive Hugo theme inspired by @spf13&amp;rsquo;s Hyde and its variant Nate Finch&amp;rsquo;s blog. It was heavily restructured with modularised page layouts for easier maintenance and modification. Hyde-hyde offers awesome features such as nice colour tone, code highlighting, Font-Awesome 5&amp;rsquo;s sidebar icons), a cool portfolio page, more choices for commenting (e.g. GraphComment, Disqus).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LaraMod</title>
      <link>https://upbeat-mcclintock-05ba11.netlify.app/portfolio/laramod/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://upbeat-mcclintock-05ba11.netlify.app/portfolio/laramod/</guid>
      <description>LaraMod is another modularisation effort to systematically organising a Laravel based project. The idea stems from my struggle to structure a Laravel-based project so that I can work effectively on individual modules whilst keeping Laravel codebase intact as much as possible and also keeping the project&amp;rsquo;s codebase separate from Laravel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>https://upbeat-mcclintock-05ba11.netlify.app/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://upbeat-mcclintock-05ba11.netlify.app/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>https://upbeat-mcclintock-05ba11.netlify.app/posts/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://upbeat-mcclintock-05ba11.netlify.app/posts/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://upbeat-mcclintock-05ba11.netlify.app/posts/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://upbeat-mcclintock-05ba11.netlify.app/posts/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Goto hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your os and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at installing hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://upbeat-mcclintock-05ba11.netlify.app/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://upbeat-mcclintock-05ba11.netlify.app/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Current Courses (Spring 2021)         ECON 306 - Microeconomic Analysis   ECON 315 - Economics of the Law    All Courses Taught Hood College (Fall 2016&amp;mdash;)         ECMG 212 - Statistics for Economics and Business   ECON 205 - Principles of Macroeconomics   ECON 304 - International Political Economy   ECON 306 - Microeconomic Analysis   ECON 316 - Game Theory   ECON 317 - Economics of Development   ECON 324 - International Trade   ECON 326 - Industrial Organization   ECON 410 - Public Economics   ECON 452 - History of Economic Thought   ECON 480 - Econometrics   MGMT 399 - Internship for Business Administration    Wake Forest University (Fall 2015&amp;mdash;Spring 2016)         ECN 150 - Introduction to Economics   ECN 272 - Austrian Economics    George Mason University (Summer 2013&amp;mdash;Summer 2015)         ECON 385 - International Economic Policy   ECON 403 - Austrian Economics   ICES High School Summer Workshops    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://upbeat-mcclintock-05ba11.netlify.app/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://upbeat-mcclintock-05ba11.netlify.app/about/</guid>
      <description>I am Assistant Professor of Economics at Hood College. Previously I taught at Wake Forest University.
I have a Ph.D and M.A. in Economics from George Mason University, and a B.A. in Economics from the University of Connecticut. Go Huskies!
My research broadly explores the political economy of innovation, technological growth, and intellectual property using the tools of new institutional economics, public choice, and market process economics.
I am a passionate user of R for data analysis, and R Markdown and GitHub for writing reproducible research, version control, and managing my workflow.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
